(INDISTINCT SPEECH)
BOY: (OVER SPEAKER) Laura?
Laura!
Laura, just don't...
Laura, do you hear me?
BOY 2: Hey! Put it down!
BOY: It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. Put it down.
GIRL: Laura, stop it!
BOY: Let's go inside...
Laura!
(BOY EXCLAIMS)
(STUDENTS SCREAM)
GIRL: Oh, God!
VAL: What the fuck?
BOY: You better slap that ho!
VAL: Yeah, whore,
I will beat your ass.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You'll beat my ass? (LAUGHS)
She's gonna beat
my ass, everybody!
(BOYS CHEERING)
Val is gonna
beat my ass. Oh!
BOY 2: Beat her up!
Good girl Val's
gonna beat my ass.
BOY 3: What the fuck?
What the fuck, bro?
BOY 4: Just get
your fucking girl.
BOY 5: Kyle,
just get out of here!
I'm going to bed.
(GIGGLING)
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
BLAIRE:
Hey. Hey, baby.
MITCH: (THROUGH MONITOR)
What's up? You okay?
Uh-huh.
You sound, like,
a little down.
Oh. No, no, no, no.
I'm great.
Okay.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHISPERING) I got
something to show you.
Ooh.
I'm excited.
Hang on real quick.
I'm gonna pee.
(MITCH URINATING)
(IN DEMONIC VOICE) Mitch.
(CHUCKLING)
Hey. I'm here.
I got something to show you.
You doing your
demon voice again?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
You like them?
Yeah.
Oh, that's so hot.
It's getting me there.
And feet, too. Yeah.
I love just the top
of toes.
BLAIRE: (IN NORMAL VOICE)
What, you... Wait.
You don't like them, do you?
No, it's just, you know,
there's other things
I wanna see more of.
Yeah, it was worth a shot.
I think I know what you want.
Yeah, let's keep
moving up.
There we go.
That's closer.
My bruised knees.
No. No, I don't wanna live there.
No? That's not it?
I don't wanna live there.
I wanna live higher.
Come on.
You're a real estate agent.
Sell this to me.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, you are now looking at
the outside of a human's right leg.
(COUGHS)
You know what?
You should just let me come over
and show you
how it's done.
No, you can't.
What do you mean,
I can't?
No. My dad
would kill you.
That's easy. Fine.
That's worth it.
I'd die for you.
You're worth it.
I want you to
take that shirt off.
Make me.
Take that shirt off
before I cut it off.
That's really violent.
Take the shirt off,
or I'll cut it off.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, that worked.
That does it for you?
All right.
Keep going.
Keep going, you're...
Faster. Come on.
(HUMMING)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want those hands down there.
No, no, no.
Back down.
(CHUCKUNG)
And I want those
panties off,
or you're gonna lose them.
You're adorable.
And really sexy
when you're violent.
Yeah?
Um...
(EXHALES)
What?
What, Miss Blue Baller?
Hey, girls get them, too.
Don't... I don't wanna hear about your balls.
That's so gross.
(LAUGHS) No, you know
what I mean. Like...
I don't know
what you mean.
I just have this mental picture of balls,
but no.
Well, I feel like you.
I don't want to experience that anymore.
Um, which is...
(SNICKERING)
Why...
Do you have
a little speech planned?
I... (LAUGHING)
Stop!
What?
I wanna make prom night the night.
Yeah?
You're serious?
Mmm-hmm.
You wouldn't lie to me?
No.
You're serious?
No, I'm not
lying to you.
That's great.
That is...
(WHOOPING)
That's finally the reaction
I was looking for.
(SING-SONG)
Two, four, six, eight!
Who do we appreciate?
Your boobies!
Your, your, your, your boobies!
Yeah.
(LAUGHS)
Let's keep
this show going.
(STAMMERING)
I wanna see what I'm getting.
Prom night.
I got something to look forward to.
Hey, we'll call him back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just getting good.
Get the knife.
Get the knife, baby.
Let's see
the whole show.
Oh, hey, guys.
JESS: Oh, shit!
KEN: What's going on?
ADAM: Oh!
KEN: Oh! Someone's
in their chonies!
JESS: What did we walk in on?
ADAM: Uh-oh.
A little cybersex!
Someone's in
their chonies!
Blaire,
you're a dirty girl.
You're going to hell now.
BLAIRE: What?
KEN: What are
you guys doing?
Going to hell
with the rest of us.
Nothing. What's up?
Hey, guys.
KEN: Where are you coming from, man?
Hey, Mitch.
Why do you have
such a big boner, bro?
(LAUGHING)
What are you talking about?
I totally missed it.
Shut up.
KEN: Hey, Blaire.
Hey, Ken.
Not funny.
How are you?
Blaire, your blouse, babe.
What?
(CHUCKLING)
What are you calling my girlfriend "babe" for?
Hey, Mitch,
who's your buddy?
What?
Who's your buddy?
Uh...
That's not with us.
What kind of sex
were you guys having?
I thought you guys
brought that in.
BLAIRE: Ken, we were
not having sex.
No, wasn't us.
Were you having a three-way?
No. What? Who is that?
ADAM: Um...
I just tried to
hang up on him.
I don't know.
It wasn't with us.
JESS: Cyber three-way!
Ken?
KEN: Yeah? Uh...
I tried to hang up on this thing.
It wouldn't let me.
JESS: You take turns?
MITCH: (STAMMERING) Honestly,
he is not in with us.
That came with you guys.
It's not working.
MITCH: All right.
KEN: All right.
BLAIRE: What do you mean?
Let's just call each other back.
Yeah?
Okay.
Bye.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(DIALING)
(LINE RINGING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
KEN: Hi!
JESS: Hi!
ADAM: Why is this fucker still here?
What, Mitch's boner?
(LAUGHING)
What is this person's problem?
KEN: Guys, guys,
it's definitely a hacker.
He's spying to get info
on farts and boners, okay?
Is that what
today's agenda is?
KEN: Well, we haven't
hit the farts yet,
but thanks to the Ken's
famous salsa,
the gas will be
rolling tonight, baby.
BLAIRE: Guys, hey.
All right, stop.
JESS: You're so gross.
Can we get rid
of this person?
Um...
How about I call
Blaire back,
and then
we'll go from there.
JESS: Bye.
KEN: Bye.
What's up?
It's still there.
So, were you guys
really cybering?
No.
Is that, like,
a thing you do?
It's...
Huh?
ADAM: It's really cute.
BLAIRE: It's still here.
ADAM: You guys
are so cute.
JESS: Hey
ADAM: Hey, guys.
JESS: Heyo!
It's still here.
Whatever, fuck it.
KEN: It's just
probably a glitch.
How do we know that?
Yeah, I can't call
the number
or anything like that.
So it's probably...
ADAM: Oh, shit!
Three stars, motherfuckers!
Suck on that!
KEN: Um... Yo,
so I talked to Kyle about Friday.
And I got the weed,
but he's out of Molly. So...
(CONVERSATION FADES)
BLAIRE: What?
JESS: Blaire, come back!
Blaire! Where'd you go?
ADAM: Stop looking at porn!
MITCH: (LAUGHING) Shut up,
for, like, a second.
JESS: Are you
talking to boys?
Hey, I'm writing
an email. Stop.
KEN: ...from the
horse's mouth.
(JESS LAUGHING)
BLAIRE: Guys, did you
talk to Val tonight?
JESS: Oh, dude,
when we were at Adam's party,
she was telling people
I had a drinking problem.
ADAM: You do.
I'm gonna add her.
Can I just be honest?
I don't like Val.
(JESS LAUGHING)
Nobody likes Val.
(DIALING)
Can I just be honest?
I don't like her.
(LINE RINGING)
The only person
that likes Val
is Val.
Is Val. Yeah.
You just get me, Jess.
ADAM: Hi, Val.
Hey, Val.
KEN: Hey, Val.
Val. Turn up the sound,
you dumb bitch.
Val!
Can you hear
me now, Ken?
KEN: Yeah, there you are, you floozy.
(JESS CHUCKLES)
Hi, yeah.
You know, when you talk
and it's muted,
I can still hear you
on your end.
So I don't appreciate
"dumb bitch."
Okay. Did you guys
buy your tickets,
like, two weeks ago
like I asked you?
KEN: No, you said you
were gonna get 'em.
VAL: No, you didn't.
No, I told you to buy them.
So now I'm hearing
that you guys
are gonna be seated
in the balcony,
and three of us are gonna
have to sit in the orchestra.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
So, maybe you should
have bought your tickets...
BLAIRE: Why?
VAL: ...sooner like I told you.
KEN: All right. What?
I don't care.
That's too bad.
I wish you bought
your ticket earlier.
Um, which seats are better,
balcony or orchestra?
Balcony.
KEN: I'll take orchestra.
Okay, you're in balcony.
I can take one more
in balcony.
I'll take it in the orchestra.
(LAUGHS)
VAL: I'm sure you will.
BLAIRE: Jess. (LAUGHING)
Oh, my God!
You're, like, the only one that got that.
BLAIRE: Val.
VAL: What?
JESS: Wait. What?
BLAIRE: Looking good.
VAL: Thank you.
BLAIRE: (CHUCKLING) No.
I got a haircut,
like, two days ago.
No. I mean,
you look good right now, too,
but check your Facebook.
VAL: What?
BLAIRE: These are
intense. Hold on.
Did you give Jess permission?
Jess! What the shit?
(LAUGHING) Dude!
VAL: Why would you
post that?
This is the first time
I'm seeing these.
These are incredible.
VAL: Oh, my God. It just
came from your account.
I've never seen these before.
Jess!
These are amazing.
Val, I didn't know
you were so much fun.
Oh, my God! A bong?
Okay, seriously,
I'm friends with my mom on here.
All right.
VAL: Come on!
KEN: Should I look at these?
Is this worth a look?
VAL: What the hell!
Delete these!
BLAIRE: Jess, take these off.
They're not good.
Dude, I didn't...
Delete them, Jess.
I didn't do this, okay?
I don't know why you're
getting so pissed at me.
Oh, my God.
You trashy little bitch.
Delete them.
Wait. Wait, did you
just call me trashy?
Are you serious?
Yeah, Jess.
So, you're asking me for a fucking favor,
to take down these photos
that I didn't post in
the fucking first place...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm asking for a favor?
I'm asking for...
You posted them.
Yeah, I didn't fucking do it, okay?
So you can be
nice to me
and I can help you...
MITCH: You guys, shut up.
BLAIRE: Girls.
...or you can suck my fucking dick...
VAL: You were the only one who
was at that fucking party.
JESS: ...and piss off.
KEN: Whoa!
Close your trashy little mouth for, like,
one second and listen to me.
BLAIRE: Girls.
Dude, I will beat your ass
any goddamn day if
you come over here, bitch.
VAL: Oh, I'm so sure.
I'm so sure.
BLAIRE: Listen, we are not ghetto.
No. Okay, how about
this? Mitch...
Blaire, really?
Do you want me to fucking
delete them or not?
Yes! Delete them now.
Look, I'll come
pick you girls up
and we can go fight outside
of a Wendy's or something...
Ken, not helping.
BLAIRE: Ken. Stop, you're not helping.
We can go to a
Taco Bell parking lot
and you guys can
slap-fight it out.
JESS: I'm deleting
them right now.
I'll pick both of you up.
Thank you, Jess.
BLAIRE: You wish.
(LAUGHING)
KEN: I am so wet right now.
VAL: They're still
here, Jess.
JESS: It's, like,
not working.
Why are you
so quick to assume
that I posted these
when I'm telling you...
VAL: Who else
would have?
JESS: I've never fucking
seen these photos before, okay?
ADAM: Oh, my God! Shut up.
I try to hit delete,
and it disappears.
I reload the page,
it's still there.
I hit delete.
I... I'm trying.
KEN: I have a headache.
I'm fucking trying to
help you. Okay, Val?
You have a headache, Ken?
You have a headache?
Okay, it looks like
it's working.
Thank you.
Okay.
Unbelievable that you
would think that would be fine.
Okay, they're gone.
KEN: No, they're not.
BLAIRE: No. Adam...
You owe me a thank you.
VAL: Adam! What the shit!
(KEN LAUGHING)
ADAM: What?
You posted some now, too?
Did you just copy
and paste them?
No. I didn't fucking post anything.
JESS: Holy shit!
BLAIRE: You guys
need to stop.
I'm a bitch, Jess?
ADAM: Chill out, Val.
Don't... Oh, you're doing
your nails right now.
Oh, you're so innocent.
I'm a bitch? Really?
ADAM: Anger issues much?
Dude, I'm not even
fucking typing.
I don't know what to say.
What is happening right now?
What the fuck?
Okay, I've dated,
like, two guys.
I didn't type that.
Fuck you, okay?
Bullshit.
KEN: Hey, just... Somebody let
me know when it's fucking over.
I love that you
think I'm a fucking slut,
and your ass is drunk...
I didn't type that!
BLAIRE: Girls, stop.
Please.
Okay, yeah, Blaire.
Just take Jess' side.
Of course.
I love you girls
so much. Let's be...
Oh, Blaire, you're just
gonna take Jess' side?
I deserve that?
No, I'm not on Jess' side.
You just typed that.
I don't think she
should have put these...
What?
No, I didn't
type anything!
Oh, if you didn't type it,
then who did?
(DOG BARKING)
Well, who the fuck
is Billie?
I told you I didn't
post those photos, Val.
Guys, who is this?
I don't know.
He was here the whole time?
BLAIRE: Ken, you said
it was just a glitch.
Well, the glitch
just typed!
(DOG BARKING)
Brucer.
KEN: Dude, I bet this guy's
been here the whole time.
JESS: I do not know a Billie,
but he apparently hates Val.
This is Laura's account.
KEN: Are you sure?
(STAMMERING)
I'm positive.
VAL: Not Laura Barns?
Yes, I'm still friends
with her on here.
I never, like,
deleted it.
JESS: Seriously?
Who is doing this?
KEN: Uh...
Maybe it's Laura.
Ken.
ADAM: Who hacks
a dead girl?
JESS: Maybe it's her
brother or something.
Why would he do that,
Jess?
JESS: He was a weirdo.
Not that weird!
KEN: It's probably just,
like, a troll or something.
What is a troll?
An Internet troll?
VAL: How do you not know what a troll is?
Like, someone that just
harasses people online.
They just wannaget
reactions out of people.
Can we hang up
on him?
KEN: No, I can't.
I can't hang up on him.
If we can't hang up...
Fine, I'll take care of him.
Hi, Billie,
listen, sweetheart.
You're a fucking asshole,
and if you don't take these down right now,
I'll come over there and knock
the trash out of your ears!
Who the fuck is this guy?
MITCH: Okay.
All right, all right,
let's stop fucking around.
Everyone, hands up,
right now.
Who's doing this?
Not me.
Adam, here we go.
I told you it wasn't me,
that's all I can say.
(DOG BARKING)
All right,
let's hang up on him.
KEN: There's, like, no...
There's no button.
VAL: What do you mean?
There is no button.
MITCH:
What do you mean?
There's no button
to hang up on him.
VAL: Guys, he's, like,
sending me something.
(DOG CONTINUES BARKING)
Oh, my God!
Where did you get this?
(DISTORTED)
This is fucked up,
do you hear me?
Brucer, shut up!
BLAIRE: Val, what is it?
KEN: Calm down, Val.
No, I can't calm down,
this is messed up!
JESS: Aw, Val, I told you
not to Snapchat your boobs.
VAL: Oh, really?
Really? That's a threat.
Yeah, you know what?
Yes, asshole, good news,
I'm calling the cops.
Congratulations,
dipshit.
(JESS CHUCKLES)
I'm calling.
Val, you don't need to
call the cops, all right?
(LINE RINGING)
Just calm down.
VAL: Yes, I do.
I do need to call the cops.
Okay? It's a threat.
Hi. Hi. Um...
Um, listen, my name is Valerie Rommel,
I'm online
and there's some asshole making
direct threats against me.
(DOG BARKING)
Brucer!
KEN: Yep
VAL: Yeah. Hold...
Ken, I swear to God,
if I find out this is you,
I will burn you alive.
You understand me?
KEN: Are you fucking kidding me?
Thanks for stopping by,
Val.
Real nice lady,
real nice chick.
She said she was gonna
burn me alive, dude.
MITCH: This isn't you, Jess?
Jess, it's not you?
No way.
Not worth my time.
ADAM: She can't do
a PowerPoint presentation.
How...
It's more...
Can't really hear you, Adam.
More than likely,
it's some girl that she's pissed off,
and she's getting
fucking scared,
and she fucking deserves it.
I'm sorry.
She takes a shit on
everyone at school.
MITCH: Should we take screen
grabs of the stuff that he was saying?
It's "Billie" with an I-E.
It's definitely a girl.
It's kind of
threatening, right?
He's been listening
this whole time.
KEN: It's not letting me
take a screen grab.
MITCH:
Yeah, me neither.
ADAM: Let's just get out of here.
Let's just hang up.
KEN: Let's just get out of here.
All right. I'll see
you guys tomorrow. Hey!
Come over, Adam,
and we'll go see, uh...
ADAM: Kyle?
We'll go across the tracks.
ADAM:
All right, I'm down.
Wait.
ADAM: What?
BLAIRE: I just got
an email from him.
MITCH: What is it?
BLAIRE: This is Laura's email.
ADAM: What'd they say?
BLAIRE: It's a link.
KEN: It's just
a stupid troll, dude.
Obvious troll is obvious.
Just send it to Ken so
he can find out who it is.
Just forward it to me.
Yeah, let Ken, like,
try to find the IP address or something.
Okay, either I'm going crazy,
or there's no forwarding button.
MITCH: It's at the bottom,
if you click on, like, "Reply All."
BLAIRE: No, I know where
it is, baby, but...
MITCH: You in Gmail?
Yeah.
Oh, my God, Blaire,
do you know how to
use a fucking computer?
Fucking open it!
BLAIRE: I do.
Share me your screen.
ADAM: Jesus.
Just forward the shit
on to Ken
so we don't have to
deal with this again.
My God.
Adam.
See, look.
It literally doesn't exist.
There's no "Forward" button.
Do you see it?
KEN: No.
JESS: Dude, weird computer shit
happens to me all the time.
Click the fucking link, dude!
KEN: Yikes.
BLAIRE: Oh, Val.
Val, you're fucking sick!
KEN: In Val's defense,
her comment wasn't
completely unwarranted, okay?
Nobody wants to
talk about it,
but I'll give you
the Ken-pinion.
Laura fucking sucked.
She was a big bully, okay,
and she deserved all the
shit she got from that video.
Ken, dude.
Come on. (LAUGHS)
BLAIRE: Ken.
What?
KEN: Sorry. I'm sorry,
that was in poor taste.
(TONE PINGING)
ADAM: "They should
lock you up."
"You monster"?
ADAM: What the...
Okay,
you're a fucking creeper.
What do you want?
Val, what'd the cops say?
ADAM: What is it?
I think it's frozen.
(DOG BARKING)
Hey, Val, you stupid bitch,
say something.
ADAM: Did you guys
hear her call?
(DOG CONTINUES BARKING)
I'm calling her.
ADAM: Guys,
look at her mirror.
KEN: Do you guys see the mirror?
The mirror's fucked up.
Yeah.
What's going
on over there?
(LINE RINGING)
Val!
KEN: Val?
Dude, maybe she's doing
this shit.
Like, for attention.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
MITCH: Blaire, is it going through?
You think of that?
Yeah, I...
Look, look at it!
It's right there.
She's not...
MITCH: Holy shit.
(CONTINUES VIBRATING)
Wait...
(LINE RINGING)
(CONTINUES VIBRATING)
(VAL SCREAMS)
KEN: What was that?
MITCH: Holy shit.
ADAM: Shit.
Val?
(DOG BARKING)
What?
Val!
MITCH: What the hell?
What just happened?
JESS: What's going on?
Did she close the computer?
Did it drop?
(BANGING ON DOOR)
MAN: Anyone home?
Hello?
BLAIRE: Hello?
KEN: Hello?
MITCH: Hey.
MAN: Fresno County Sheriff's Office.
Somebody called 911?
(DOOR OPENS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hello?
MITCH: Can they hear us?
Hello, hey!
Down at the computer!
Hello?
Hey!
MAN: Dispatch, we got a...
Hello?
JESS: Hello, can you hear us?
Wait, what'd they say?
KEN: 10-35?
MITCH: I heard 10-25.
Which one?
KEN: 10-30.
MITCH: 10-25.
What is that?
10-35...
No, it's a time check, so...
MITCH: That's insane.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
5250?
MITCH: 5250?
I didn't hear 5250.
No, it's a mental...
(GASPS)
MITCH: No shit.
Val used to have seizures!
MAN: Yeah,
we'll start around the... Guys, she...
KEN: Are you sure?
I don't remember.
Yeah, she told me,
like, a long time ago.
She had this sickness
that causes seizures.
Maybe she just had
a frickin' seizure.
ADAM: Have you ever seen
her have a seizure, ever?
MAN: Jesus.
This is a 10-55.
No, dude,
they said 10-55.
10-55?
MITCH: 10-55?
10-55...
10-55 is suicide.
Did they really
just say 10-55?
(JESS SCREAMS)
Val?
JESS: Oh, my God.
MITCH: Hey! Hey!
ADAM: Hey!
Hello? Hello?
MITCH: Shit.
ADAM: Shit.
MITCH: Okay.
All right, I'm calling.
Does anyone know
her parents' number?
KEN: I'll try to
get her back, okay?
KEN: Nobody accept.
No one accept it.
What...
BLAIRE: Who are you?
BLAIRE: What did he send
you guys?
What?
KEN: I can't fucking
shut it off.
We gotta get him out.
MITCH: Who cares?
We have to go over and help Val.
Okay? We can do
this shit after.
Wait, wait, hold on.
The cops are with Val.
MITCH: Yeah, we're doing
this shit after.
What's the point?
Hold on.
What are you guys gonna
do that the cops can't do?
Fuck this! All right.
We're not doing this here.
Everyone, just fucking stop.
Pick up your phone,
mute your computers.
I don't know where
my phone is, guys.
Seriously,
please don't do this.
Hold on, Jess...
(INAUDIBLE)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Fuck, guys.
Guys?
ADAM: ...Val's in five minutes.
MITCH: Whatever he's doing,
it can wait, okay?
JESS: Guys, loan hear you.
He can hear you.
He can turn your mics on.
KEN: Guys, can you just
fucking trust me, okay?
Install this program
and I'll find out who it is.
MITCH: You serious?
ADAM: Who cares, dude?
Val's in fucking trouble.
You just saw her.
MITCH: Okay,
everyone relax.
BLAIRE: Ken can
get him out, okay?
We need to stop this guy.
JESS: Please, Billie,
just let us leave, okay?
KEN: You guys wanna know
who this is or not?
Yeah, we're ready
to play, Billie.
Jess, we're gonna play a game.
What's going on, guys?
I don't know what's happening!
We're gonna play a game, okay?
You wanna play the game.
Jess, you wanna play the game.
JESS: Okay.
MITCH: Okay, is it fixed?
JESS: What is it?
It's just a game.
We're just all
gonna download it
and play it, right?
I'm not doing anything, man.
I just wanted to play a game.
You like games.
You seem to like games.
Dude, I thought
we were gonna play.
All right.
I have a fucking
great game for you, man.
Okay, you guys got it?
BLAIRE: Yeah.
MITCH: Okay.
I just launched it.
I got something
for you, Billie.
KEN: Fucking shit.
Okay, okay, okay.
Is it searching, guys?
Did everybody download it?
BLAIRE: Mine's got something.
Mine's got something.
Okay, good. Wait till
everybody got something.
Is it flagging?
Has everybody got some flags?
It should be more than one, too.
It should be multiple.
JESS: Yeah.
Okay, cool.
BLAIRE: Yes.
Okay, hit "Trash."
Trash all of those and
then empty your recycling bins, okay?
Yeah,
empty your recycling bin
after you trash it.
Do not save them.
Everything.
Everything that's flagged.
MITCH: It's not gonna
delete these.
Just fucking listen to me.
Trust me, dude.
MITCH: Shit. Shit.
JESS: Okay.
(STAMMERING) Is it deleted?
What's going on?
Keep me updated, guys.
Okay. Okay, Adam's
is done. Mitch?
Mine's the same.
Okay, Jess?
Mine's done.
Okay, Blaire?
Blaire? Blaire!
MITCH: Shit.
BLAIRE: There's a lot
in my recycling bin.
I don't know how to
make it go faster.
MITCH: What?
ADAM: I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Adam,
don't make him mad.
MITCH: She's right.
Adam, you are overreacting.
He's got...
KEN: It's gonna be fine.
We just need...
BLAIRE: Just stop.
We're just waiting
on Blaire's bin, guys.
Everything is gonna
be cool, I promise.
Blaire...
There's a pinwheel,
I don't...
Why is he counting down?
MITCH: Don't listen to him.
Don't worry about it.
Just get it done.
KEN: Okay.
It's cool, Blaire.
BLAIRE: All right, it's done!
Everything's... It's done.
KEN: It's done?
It's done? It's gone?
Yes.
ADAM: Thank God.
Is it gone?
Is he out?
MITCH: Yeah. Yeah.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Fuck you, Billie.
Suck on that, bitch!
(KEN TAPPING ON TABLE)
Thank you, Ken.
Adam, you pulled out
a fucking gun!
JESS: Dude,
what the hell was that?
(LAUGHING)
MITCH: Did you load that thing?
Yeah, man.
You were flinging it around!
It's going to go off.
KEN: Oh, my fucking God.
MITCH: I can't believe it.
Were you gonna shoot...
What were you gonna do,
shoot through
the computer?
Guys! Guys,
I saved your life.
We just...
Val used to get seizures.
I mean,
that's the only thing
I can think of.
MITCH: We should call the cops.
MITCH: Okay.
I had a conversation
on my computer...
(LINE RINGING)
FEMALE OPERATOR: (OVER PHONE)
911, please state your emergency.
ADAM: Yeah, hi,
there's someone threatening
me and my friends online,
and they also threatened our friend,
Valerie Rommel.
You sent some officers over
there earlier to her house,
but they didn't see
what we saw,
and there's a lot more
to the story. So...
What is your
friend's address?
What?
Her address.
Uh, guys?
Guys, what's her address?
JESS: Uh, hold on,
I have it in my desk.
Hold on.
ADAM: One sec.
JESS: 10705 East Bauer.
ADAM: Yeah,
it's 10705 East Bauer.
And he keeps
threatening us,
and he won't
leave us alone, and...
Where are you right now, sir?
Um, I'm at home.
Online, with my friends.
Are you safe?
Yeah.
All of you?
Yeah, we're good.
Even Ken?
What?
Don't hang up.
JESS: But what
just happened?
(SHUSHING)
I said, "Don't hang up."
BLAIRE: Who did you call?
Fuck! It's this
fucking asshole!
Hey, genius,
we can see you!
Hey! Hey, buddy!
Uh...
You know what?
What is that?
It's behind, like, a lattice?
Like, a crate
or something? Like...
It's not letting me
hang up.
JESS: Wait, Ken! Ken!
KEN: What?
Wait, come back.
Uh...
Back up a little bit.
Why?
Just do it, dude.
(THUDDING)
(OBJECTS CRASHING)
(SCRAPING)
Ken, what the fuck's
going on?
(DIALING)
(LINE RINGING)
Ken.
(KEN SCREAMING)
MITCH: What the fuck?
BLAIRE: Ken? Ken?
KEN: Don't kill me!
BLAIRE: Ken!
JESS: Is he okay?
Ken!
(SCREAMING)
Oh, my God! Ken! Ken...
ADAM: Ken, come on!
Ken, stop fucking around!
BLAIRE: Oh, my God!
No! Don't...
JESS: Guys...
MITCH: Holy shit!
BLAIRE:
What was he doing?
JESS: (CRYING)
What the fuck just happened? Ken?
Shut up, Jess!
Just shut up!
JESS: What the fuck?
ADAM: Shut up, Jess! Fuck!
This is so fucked up!
BLAIRE: This isn't funny anymore!
ADAM: Fuck this shit! Okay?
I'm fucking out of here!
You hear me?
(DOOR SLAMS)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
ADAM: Fuck.
(THUD)
Hey, babe,
go look your door.
Go look your door.
BLAIRE: What? I...
I think it is locked.
ADAM: Hello?
Hello?
Oh, fuck.
What do you see?
Adam?
Adam,
what do you see?
ADAM: Guys...
(ADAM BREATHING HEAVILY)
ADAM: There's fucking
no one here.
I'm gonna go check it out.
No, no, no.
Don't. Don't.
JESS: No, don't do it.
No, Adam, no!
JESS: Don't go outside.
ADAM: What?
(SHUSHES)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
ADAM: What the...
Is it locked?
Lock the door.
Lock your door.
ADAM: Yeah, I fucking...
Who's there? Hey!
(MUSIC PLAYING
IN ADAM'S HOUSE)
Who's here?
I have a fucking gun!
You hear me?
(LOUD THUD)
Fuck. What the fuck?
What do you want?
BLAIRE: What video?
VAL: What the fuck?
BOY: You better slap that ho!
VAL: Yeah, whore,
I will beat your ass.
LAURA: You'll beat my ass?
(LAUGHS)
She's gonna beat
my ass, everybody!
Val is gonna beat my ass!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
BOY: ...slap that ho!
...slap that ho!
LAURA: Val is gonna
beat my ass!
...beat my ass, everybody!
(VIDEOS PLAYING AT ONCE)
ADAM: No, this isn't on us, man.
JESS: This isn't our fault.
ADAM: This is not on us.
(ADAM BREATHING HEAVILY)
ADAM: What?
What?
No. No, fuck this.
I'm not...
I'm not fucking
playing any fucking...
(THUDDING)
Adam! Adam, stop!
MITCH: What? What?
Like the drinking game?
What? Wait, how do you play?
How do you play?
MITCH: I'm not playing
your fucking games.
Why don't you
fucking explain it.
It's your fucking game, man!
Somebody just tell me how to play!
Guys... Jess, how do you...
Dude, you... Okay,
you put up five fingers,
and then if you've
done something,
you have to put
your finger down.
That's how it works.
This is the dumbest
fucking thing.
Wait.
Why are you... Why?
(CRYING)
I'm gonna lose.
MITCH: Are we doing this?
I don't wanna play.
Put your hands up.
Put your hands up!
Just fucking do it.
Fine, all right,
five fingers up, fine.
Who did that?
Wasn't fucking me.
Okay, fuck,
it was me, okay?
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
You said it was Val.
Okay, I lied, all right?
You...
It's not like there's not some
kind of truth in there!
Jess,
what are you doing?
Dude, it's not my fault!
Why are you doing that to me?
You're the one who's like,
"I'm not hungry, I already ate."
All that shit.
MITCH: Do not do this right now.
It wasn't fucking me.
It was one of you guys?
MITCH: Jess, stop it!
Don't attack people right now.
You know how much fucking
trouble I got in for that shit?
I'm sorry,
it was me, okay?
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
We were drunk,
and it happened,
and I didn't know
how to tell you.
Fuck you!
I'm sorry, Jess.
Great friend, Blaire.
I have apologized.
She's not apologized for
starting this rumor thing about me.
That is not true,
by the way.
Hey! We're keeping
together on this. Stop it.
That was me. Easy.
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
It was last year.
She kissed me.
I threw her off.
Nothing happened.
It's fine.
What? No, no,
please tell me he's lying,
Jess, you fucking bitch!
Fuck you.
It wasn't me, okay?
Shut up. Shut up!
Blaire?
It was me, man.
Hey, it was me.
It was you?
I'm sorry. Yeah.
What? Why?
What do you mean, "What? Why?"
Does it really
fucking matter?
Yeah,
it does to me,
Mitch!
They put me in fucking handcuffs, man!
Guys, stop it!
I almost had a record!
My fucking dad almost
disowned me for that!
Dude, it was gonna be
both of us or one of us,
and I would do
the same shit for you.
So let me take the rap, huh?
Hey, it doesn't matter!
It doesn't matter!
Exactly, it doesn't matter!
Yeah?
Oh, my fucking hero, Mitch.
Hey! Knock it Off!
My hero!
Oh, fuck. You guys
are fucked up, man!
Yeah, like you don't have
enough fucking money, okay?
Oh, keep it, bitch!
Fucking asshole.
Oh, yeah, let's listen
to Blaire again,
'cause that keeps working
out so fucking well.
What?
Guys,
are you serious?
None of us did that.
We wouldn't do that.
Blaire?
What?
Blaire,
did you do that?
No!
How do we know?
Hey! It's not her.
It's not her.
I... We wouldn't do that.
Put down a finger and we'll see.
She already said it.
Stop pushing her!
Yeah, I heard her say that!
She always tells the truth,
Mitch?
Yeah! Yeah.
Oh, she does?
She always tells
the truth, right?
'Cause you always tell the truth,
right, Blaire?
You always tell the truth.
Fine, it was me.
Adam, Jesus!
You piece of shit!
You're a fucking piece of shit.
You know that?
Oh, fuck you!
You're a piece of shit!
JESS: I'm just nothing to you, Adam.
You piece of shit.
Mitch, stop!
Oh, fuck you!
He said if I traded you that
the three of us could live.
I was trying to save your life, Mitch.
MITCH: No!
(ALL TALKING AT ONCE)
JESS: I hate you!
(CRYING)
I hate you!
I hate you, Adam!
'Cause you guys are all
so fucking perfect, right? Yeah?
Wait, wait, wait.
Guys, guys, guys.
Come on. Come on, please.
Okay, okay.
All right. I see.
You know what?
Fuck this.
Guys, come on.
Hey, I got an idea.
Just play the stupid game.
Hey, Billie,
why don't you lay off?
I got this one.
JESS: What the fuck
are you doing?
Easy one.
Never have I ever had sex.
Hey, Billie, can we get
a timer, please?
What are you doing right now?
Oop! There goes
my finger.
Hey, Jess, you only need to
put down one, not 50.
Fuck you, Adam.
Oh, okay. Whoa!
Hey, that's weird.
The timer's still going.
Hey, Billie, why's the timer still going, huh?
What are you doing?
Tick-tock...
What are you doing, Adam?
The round ain't over.
What are you doing?
Someone hasn't answered.
Hello?
What are you...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mitch.
What do you mean?
Oh, okay, new question.
BLAIRE: I'm sorry...
Never have I ever
fucked my boyfriend's
best friend.
BLAIRE: What are
you doing, Adam?
There.
You happy, Blaire?
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing?
Is he serious?
Mitchie, I'm so sorry.
Don't...
JESS: What?
Are you serious?
He's telling the truth?
God damn it, Adam!
What do you mean?
It was an accident.
It was an accident!
MITCH: It was an accident?
I didn't mean
to do that, Adam.
Oh, my God!
I was drunk, okay?
Oh, my God.
What were you doing?
It just...
I'm sorry, it just...
How? How?
I don't get it. How?
I hate you, Adam!
Fuck you, Blaire.
Stop talking,
Adam! Stop it!
But, hey,
it doesn't matter,
remember, Mitch?
It doesn't
fucking matter, right?
It does matter.
It does matter, because...
We might all fucking die,
but we're better than you,
you piece of shit!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
BLAIRE: Guys, stop.
Guys, please stop.
(ALL ARGUING)
JESS: Any other guy
I liked treated me like shit.
MITCH: I'm gonna fucking win this thing.
I'm gonna win this thing.
Never... Never have I ever...
Everyone's hands up!
We're still playing!
We're still playing here!
Never have I ever
roofied Ashley Dane!
Fuck you, man! Okay?
Guys, what are we doing?
Oh, look at that!
Finger's down!
We were drunk.
She's a fucking liar.
Look at that!
That's how
you wanna play?
All right. Fine.
Guys, come on.
Please, let's stop!
Don't talk to me.
I don't wanna hear from you, slut.
Fucking slut.
Please don't call me that.
Do not call me that.
How many guys, huh?
How many guys?
No more, I swear!
Do you think I'm a slut?
Are you kidding me?
Oh, you swear?
Like you swore you love me?
No!
Mitchie, I love you!
Perfect fucking Blaire.
It only...
You don't even know!
It only lasted,
like, a second!
Oh, fuck you,
Blaire!
Why would you tell me that?
Right, Adam? It only...
That doesn't make shit better.
I'm sorry, baby.
I don't know what else to say. I'm sorry.
Mitch, I...
MITCH: Fucking...
Never... Never have I ever forced
Ashley Dane to get an abortion!
Stop doing this, guys.
I'm sorry, okay?
Everybody just...
Oh, it's four!
It's four!
What are you...
Don't fucking do this, man.
It's four.
Fuck you!
You fucking took my girl,
and you took her
for yourself.
No, he didn't. I'm still...
It wasn't like that, man.
It wasn't like that!
Mitch...
It wasn't?
It wasn't like that?
ADAM: No, it wasn't!
It fucking wasn't!
BLAIRE: (CRYING)
Why is this happening?
Why are you showing this?
Mitchie, don't watch!
Just don't watch, okay?
Don't read into her shit,
okay? Don't watch.
It didn't...
Baby, it didn't mean
anything. I love you.
Stop watching.
Look at me, Mitch.
Mitch, look at me!
I didn't mean it.
Guys?
We were drunk, Mitch, okay?
It was my birthday.
Oh, fuck you!
I sent you a fucking card,
you piece of shit.
JESS: No!
No! Bullshit.
Fuck you!
I'm ready for you,
motherfucker!
You hear me?
I'm fucking ready for you!
Come on over! Now!
I'll fucking kill you!
I'm gonna...
(PRINTER WHIRRING)
Fuck.
It's my printer.
Fuck!
What? What, Adam?
What is it?
MITCH: What is it?
ADAM: Fuck.
What is it?
It says I'm not supposed
to tell you what it says.
Oh, come on, Adam.
Don't do this to us.
Don't do this to us!
Please don't do this to us!
JESS: What's it say?
(PRINTER WHIRRING)
Tell us right now,
you piece of shit.
You fucked my girl.
I fucking told you I loved you.
You fucked her. Fuck...
Oh, Mitch. You're never
gonna find out, okay?
So get your narrow fucking head around that,
you hear me?
What's it say?
MITCH: What is it?
I can't.
ADAM: Fuck.
You can't?
Oh, Adam and Blaire with
another fucking secret.
No, no, no.
No. It's not like that, man.
It's not like that.
You don't understand, okay?
MITCH: I'm fucking finished.
I'm signing off.
Mitch, it's not
like that, baby.
No, no, no!
She'll kill you!
She'll kill you.
Stop it!
You're gonna kill me?
Hey, if you're
gonna kill me,
you better fucking
kill me right now!
No! Stop, baby, okay?
Mitch. Mitch...
Just calm down.
Just calm down, okay?
...just calm down, okay, man?
Everybody just calm down.
Okay? Everybody just...
Baby? It's okay. It's...
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you.
MITCH: Look at me.
Look at me.
You have one minute.
Say what you want.
What?
Okay, okay, okay.
It, um... It just...
We met up
one more time to see
if it was a fluke or something more,
okay?
Okay. Where was this?
ADAM: It was at my house.
You shut up!
Shh... Adam.
Where? When?
Just let me talk to him.
Let me talk to him.
It was in September right
before we went back to school, okay?
We just...
We started to do it,
but then we stopped
because it was
really clear, okay?
It didn't...
She's not lying, man.
Shut up! Shut up!
Adam, stop.
Did he touch you again?
Did he touch you again down there?
Just for a second, okay?
Just for a second.
ADAM: She's not lying,
Mitch. She's not, okay?
Okay?
MITCH: Now show me the paper.
You don't want me to
show you the paper.
No, I do, Blaire.
Show me the paper.
No, Mitch,
why are you doing this?
No more fucking secrets.
Blaire, I'm not fucking around.
Show me the paper.
Or I walk!
No, no, no!
Please don't leave me!
That's it, Blaire.
Show me the paper...
You gotta understand...
MITCH: I'm not fucking around, here!
Show me that paper!
Sit the fuck...
Get back here, Mitch!
BLAIRE: What are you... No, no, no!
Mitch, come back here! No!
BLAIRE: Oh, my God!
(RAPID BEEPING)
(JESS SCREAMING)
No! No! No!
JESS: Adam!
You stupid bitch!
I'm sorry, Jess.
You killed him.
(BOTH CRYING)
I didn't know what to do.
MALE AUTOMATED VOICE:
Hello. Can I share
a secret with you?
It's just three words.
Free live cams.
Free live cams
are the absolute best.
Having beautiful women
all over the Internet
just waiting to fulfill
your every desire.
BLAIRE: No.
There's simply nothing
better than that.
BLAIRE: I'm not gonna
just sit here, guys.
Adam...
Adam was right, okay?
We can't listen to her.
I'm gonna make this right, guys, okay?
I didn't do anything.
Jess, just do not answer,
do not give in!
What?
Don't answer.
Whatever you do, do not answer.
(LOUD THUD)
(SCREAMING)
Oh, my God!
Jess? Jess, just run.
(LOUD THUD)
Just hide, Jess.
Just hide in your bathroom.
(CRYING)
I'm gonna get you help!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
God.
Yes! Okay. Hi!
Guys, listen, look at me!
Hey, look at me. Hi, hi.
My name is Blaire Lily,
and I need help.
No! Hello!
Hi! Hello!
Hi! My name is Blaire Lily,
and I need help.
I need your help.
Don't be a... Come on.
Hello?
No.
Hi. Hi.
Can you hear me?
Hi, can you hear me?
Hi. Hi. My name is
Blaire Lily, and... No! Shit!
You want some?
Hi. You want some?
Hi!
Hey, guys! Hello!
RANDO: Hey.
Hi.
Can you hear me?
RANDO: Hey.
Something is happening...
RANDO: Something is happening.
DANK: Can I tell you...
It's happening right now.
Hey! Just...
I am being attacked!
DANK: She's saying...
I need you to
call the police!
RANDO: Shut up!
She's being attacked!
Please.
Police, yes, the police.
DANK: We're gonna call the police.
I will do anything you want.
Dial the Fresno, California...
DANK: Police.
Please call them.
Police!
Stop being pricks!
Oh, God!
Hello?
Can you help me?
Are you okay?
I... Listen, I...
There's something happening.
Like, my friend is being attacked.
She needs your help.
How can I help?
Can I help you?
Yes, yes.
Can you call the Fresno,
California Police and tell them that...
My name is Blaire Lily.
Look, here's her address.
Look, look.
Here's her address...
Okay, one second.
Okay. Here.
Okay, one minute.
4478 Winslow Avenue.
Hi, there's this girl,
and she's online,
and she says that there's
someone attacking her.
She's in Fresno,
California.
Who's attacking you?
Who? I don't know.
There's something in my house...
She's just yelling a lot.
...and we're being attacked.
She says there's something in
her house and she's being attacked,
and it's her boyfriend
and all of her friends.
Just tell them to
come to that address.
You know who's
attacking you?
Okay. She says just
come to the address.
Wait,
what is it again?
What's the address?
Yes, I'll tell...
I'm sending it to you right now.
Sorry, one minute.
I... I just...
Come on!
Okay. So the address
is 4478 Winslow Avenue.
And she said it was
in Fresno, California.
Just tell them to get here!
Are they coming?
Are you...
They're going to send a car.
They are? They are?
Thank you!
Okay.
Okay, great.
Yeah, they said they're five minutes away.
They're five minutes?
Okay. Okay.
Okay, Jess.
There's a car coming.
The cops are coming.
They're going to be
there in 5 minutes.
Why are they taking so much...
The cops are coming.
BLAIRE: (SOFTLY) What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Jess?
Jess! Jess! Just run.
Jess, just run, okay?
Just...
(MUMBLING)
(JESS SCREAMING)
BLAIRE: Jess!
No. Jess? Jess?
(CHOKING)
No! No! Oh, my God!
What?
I'm so...
(SCREAMS)
(DISTORTED)
Oh, my God!
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Mitch?
(CLATTERING)
Oh, my God.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, my God!
(MUFFLED BREATHING)
What are you doing?
(BOTH SOBBING)
Mitchie.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
BLAIRE: Do you see...
BLAIRE: Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
(ALARM BEEPING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
What is that?
It's an alarm I set for tomorrow.
We have a test.
We do?
Yeah, it's...
Mitch,
do you hate me?
I don't hate you,
Blaire.
You don't?
No, I don't hate you.
I love you so much.
I love you.
That wasn't us, Laura!
Laura, please.
It was not us, I promise you.
It wasn't us.
Please, Laura.
It wasn't us!
BLAIRE: I'm scared.
MITCH: Laura,
I promise you.
(BLAIRE WHIMPERING)
Mitch!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
Why did you do...
Mitch? Mitch?
Mitch!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
What?
Guys, I'm so sorry!
Why did you do that?
What... Who was...
What?
(TIMER COUNTING DOWN)
No, no, no.
Why are you still counting down?
Why are you...
What do you want from me?
What do you think I did?
(BLAIRE SNIFFLING)
We were sisters, Laura.
Don't you know it?
I loved you.
Look.
Look at us.
No, look at us. Look!
Do you remember that?
I'm so sorry we drifted apart.
What?
(COUNTDOWN STOPS)
No!
I got her. (LAUGHING)
I'm sorry.
(DOOR CREAKING)
BLAIRE: No!
(SOFTLY) Laura?
(SCREAMING)